This week's story on Rainbow Club.
You have a guest.
The Rainbow Club members have an unexpected guest.
Preparing to move to a new house, I have no place to go.
So I stay at Kian84's house.
We have a Tekken match and go to a karaoke.
(Hyun Moo is immersed in the song.)
Tough girls gather.
They enjoy all kinds of food together...
and talk about guys. How would they spend a day together?
Pose like this or face forward.
- Try something else like this.
-  That's...
Here's another tough girl.
Dreaming of becoming like Angelina Jolie,
she learns stunt skills.
Push. That's good.
Where am I?
"What is your name?"
The legendary singer, Yang Hee Eun visits Kim Ban Jang's house.
Ban Jang is nervous all day.
He's afraid of being scolded by his senior singer.
Kim Ban Jang.
(He is startled.)
I Live Alone, "Welcome to My House".
Welcome to my house
(It's a hot day in August at Hyun Moo's house.)
(The alarm wakes him up.)
(He's tossing on his bed.)
(Gosh, I'm tired.)
(It's 7:30am.)
(I have to get up now.)
(He looks very tired.)
I should start packing.
(What are you rushing for?)
Today, my lease expires, so I have to move out.
However, I can't move in to my new house today.
I have to wait for 15 days.
So I had to find a place to stay.
I remembered Kian84 told me that I could stay at his house.
(This is when he invited Kian84 and Ban Jang to his house.)
My move-in date is on 25th, but I have to move out on the 10th.
- I have to wait for 15 days.
-  What will you do?
Come to my house. You can stay with me.
Can I?
I have a queen size bed. We can sleep together.
- In that room?
-  Let's sleep together.
In the room with a scary painting?
We always help each other out.
We're the icon of mutual help.
I decided to stay at his house for a while.
How many days am I going to stay at his house?
(Hyun Moo packs his clothes to wear for 15 days.)
It feels surreal.
Shorts.
(He packs a T-shirt and a pair of shorts.)
(That would be enough.)
He probably doesn't have much food there. Goodness.
(He goes to the kitchen to pack food.)
(What's in my fridge?)
I have nothing to pack.
(What food is he taking out from his fridge?)
(It's frozen food.)
Dumplings.
I should give him some alcohol drinks.
Here it is.
(It's a perfect gift for the person who loves drinking.)
Let's give him an expensive one. It's champagne.
(Next, he searches the cupboard.)
(I have canned tuna, instant rice and ramyeon.)
(This would be enough for a while.)
(He packed only a pair of clothes,)
(but he's packing a lot of food.)
I think I'm done.
(He's ready to stay with Kian84.)
I should call him.
Is he sleeping?
Hello?
- Hi, Kian84.
-  Hi, Hyun Moo.
You know I'm going to your house in the evening, right?
Sure. Come over and hang out.
I'm not going there to hang out. I'll stay there for a few days.
For how long?
- For 15 days.
-  For 15 days?
For 15 days. Okay.
Hold on.
Have you bought an air conditioner?
- I bought one yesterday.
-  Okay.
- I'll go to your house after work.
- See you soon.
-  See you.
They're here.
(The movers arrived.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Hello. Please come in.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Wow, you arrived at exactly 8am.
Do I have a lot to pack?
I think it'll be about six tonnes.
Usually, a four-member family has this much.
- It's a lot for a single man.
-  Is it?
- I have less stuff than last time.
-  That's right.
- I don't see your dining table.
-  I gave some out.
Would you charge me less then?
- That doesn't make any difference.
-  Is that so?
Please tell us if you have any valuables or fragile items.
Valuables?
You should carry those with you.
- My pictures.
-  Okay.
- Please take good care of them.
-  I understand.
- Especially that one.
-  Okay.
(Please take good care of me.)
- Just be careful not to break them.
-  Okay.
Excuse me. We can't pack what's in here.
- Do you mean the food?
-  Yes.
I see.
I didn't expect the food would be a problem.
What should I do with these peaches?
(He takes out the peaches.)
I should give them to Kian84.
I'm sure he doesn't have any fruit.
I'll pack the food in that tiny bag.
- Is there anything to eat in here?
-  Yes.
- Like frozen sagol?
I'll eat this for dinner tonight.
(While Hyun Moo is packing food in the kitchen,)
(the mover puts Wilson in a box.)
(Pressing)
(I'm not to be packed in here.)
(Since we found you, we have to pack you.)
(The movers move everything out of the house quickly.)
(He's waiting outside to let them work freely.)
Where is Wilson?
(He realises that Wilson is gone.)
I think they packed Wilson.
- Excuse me.
-  Yes?
- There was a stuffed bear.
-  I saw it. A white bear.
- That's right.
-  It's...
packed with couch cushions.
- Is it in the box with cushions?
-  Yes.
- Do you need to find it?
-  No.
- You don't have to.
-  I'll find it for you.
That's okay.
- Do you know where it is?
-  Yes.
(He feels apologetic to both the mover and Wilson.)
I should've put Wilson aside.
(Wilson, wait. I'm coming.)
(Fortunately, the mover found the box quickly.)
I think this is it.
- Is that it?
-  Yes.
I see the fur.
(Finally, the box is opened.)
Oh, my.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
- I'll carry this.
-  Okay.
(He's caressing Wilson.)
You must've been scared.
He's scared. He's crying.
I'm sorry.
(Please take good care of me from now on.)
(He's holding Wilson tightly.)
(The movers are done packing.)
- I'll see you on 26th.
-  Okay.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
Goodbye. See you in 15 days.
(He's back to his empty house.)
The house looks like a model home now.
(There's nothing left to show that he lived here for two years.)
Two years ago, I was sitting right here...
thinking how I should decorate the house.
I'm exhausted.
(Two years ago, he imagined how his new house would look.)
(However, the reality was different from what he imagined.)
I'll keep my new house neat and tidy.
It's an important place.
In this house, I did a lot of thinking, rest and fun.
It's been a place to regain energy.
Things went well while I was living here as well.
It helped me move forward.
I'm grateful to this house.
Let's go, Wilson. I have to go to work now.
We'll go to a weird place later. Don't be surprised.
(He puts Wilson on his suitcase.)
(It's uncomfortable.)
(The suitcase falls.)
I should've just left you in the box.
(That's mean.)
Hang in there.
Goodbye.
(Goodbye, my old sweet home.)
(In the late afternoon, the sun is scorching.)
(Under the sun, there's Kian84's house.)
(Hyun Moo arrives after work.)
Kian84! Kian84!
Oh. Hi, Hyun Moo.
I'll go out.
- How did you come here?
-  By car.
- Did you?
-  Yes.
Please carry the peaches.
- What?
-  Thank you for this.
You don't look happy with my gift.
- I'm afraid I might be criticised.
-  You can be happy.
- Why would you be criticised?
-  I was criticised for taking gifts.
You need to be strong. Don't let criticisms get you down.
- How...
-  Let's enjoy the peaches.
(They rush in to avoid the heat.)
- You have more furniture. What?
-  The air conditioner...
It's not yet set up.
(Hyun Moo's hope is sealed up.)
(I'm sorry.)
You haven't even opened the boxes?
It's funny how people's feelings change.
Once I saw the boxes of the air conditioner,
I thought of my other three friends.
"Should I call him?"
I told myself to sneak out of his house when he was asleep...
after having a good day with him.
I had so much going on in my head at that moment.
Since a lot of people buy an air conditioner in this season,
- I have to wait 10 days.
-  It's a busy season?
I expected a cool breeze in your house.
I have a fan, though.
That's just noisy.
I'll put it on full blast.
Is this a heater?
No, it's a fan.
It will be cooler soon.
The movers took my stuff out of my house this morning.
All I have now is my suitcase.
How many days will you stay here?
For about 10 days.
Will you really stay for 10 days?
I need your permission. I can't stay just because I want to.
(For 10 days?)
- You don't look...
-  It'd be an honour for me.
You don't look so happy about it.
I'm happy. It'd be an honour for me.
You look very different from when I gave you my furniture.
- You said you didn't use the table.
-  That one?
That's true. I rarely use it.
- I can do everything on this table.
-  You can eat and work here.
- Okay. I'll give it to you.
-  Thank you.
- You can have it.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
I got criticised for taking that table.
(He was criticised for receiving the table.)
I brought it because you said you weren't using it.
- Why do you care what they think?
-  I read a lot of harsh comments.
- Someone called me a beggar.
-  What did they say?
Pardon?
"Why does he keep asking to give him things?"
"Why would he try to take all those when he's making a lot of money?"
- Did you read all the comments?
-  I read a few. I stopped reading...
- because it hurt my feelings.
-  I see.
- They called me a beggar.
-  No way.
Don't let it bother you. Being a celebrity isn't easy.
What?
- This is just the beginning.
-  What are you talking about?
When people criticise my webtoon characters,
it feels like I'm hiding behind the characters.
I understand.
But this time, they criticised me.
Are you hurt?
- Because you took the table,
-  Yes.
it took less time to move out today.
- Are you sure you'll be okay?
-  I forgot.
I should put the food in the refrigerator.
My fridge is too small for all of them.
I brought frozen dumplings. I haven't even opened them.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
- Let's put them in the fridge...
-  Let's share the food.
- and share it.
-  Okay.
Do you know what this is? This is awesome.
Isn't it sagol?
My friend who runs a barbecue restaurant...
froze this for me.
- It's frozen?
-  Let's eat it together.
(Let's eat sagol for dinner.)
I should put the sagol out...
if we're going to eat it tonight.
It takes an hour to defrost it.
Let's put this...
(He puts it on the table to defrost it.)
- It's good for your health.
-  Thank you.
Please don't mention it.
I should be thanking you for letting me stay here.
- But...
-  It must be hot in my house.
I didn't know it'd be this hot.
I slept in a motel the other day because it was too hot.
Is there a motel near here?
Yes, there is. Shall we go to a motel?
Don't be surprised if I disappear at night.
Let's sleep in a motel together.
Shall we? Would you like to do that?
- Shall we do that?
-  Pardon?
- What do you say?
-  I'd love to. It's cool there.
Let's sleep here...
and go to a motel if we can't stand the heat.
We should.
You went to a motel to avoid the heat?
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your clothes?
- Sure, I'll find...
-  Can I?
Shall I find you something comfortable?
- We are the same size.
-  You can wear these.
- Did you wash them?
-  Yes, I did.
It's so hot.
(He washed them a long time ago.)
Change into comfortable clothes.
It's even hotter in here.
I don't sleep in that room because it's too hot.
Are these your bathing suit?
I wear those pants whenever I work near the deadline.
You don't need to wear underwear since it has inner pants.
We're not close enough to share underwear yet.
(They're too short for him.)
(They look like twins.)
Would you like to drink something?
I feel like I'm in a lookout shed.
I can't stand it. It's too hot.
It feels like...
It reminds me of the military training camp.
- You brought that?
-  Yes.
(He's holding the bag of sagol.)
- Are you feeling better?
-  It's so cool.
(It's cool.)
You can stay for 10 days.
- Are you sure you'll be okay?
-  I snore.
- Do you?
-  Yes.
I can just sleep in the office.
- Since you're staying here...
-  I can't let you do that.
- Let's sleep here together.
-  You want to get good comments?
It's not that.
If you sleep in your office and I sleep in your house,
You keep giving me presents.
Both of us were criticised once.
I was criticised about the drawing.
(Kian84 drew a portrait of him.)
This is amazing.
(He sold the drawing with a good intention.)
It's a meaningful event.
(How could he sell a gift just because he doesn't like it?)
Don't you think it's a nice drawing?
I was criticised because of your drawing.
You were criticised because of my table.
I was surprised how people criticised me like that.
- Don't worry about it.
-  Okay.
- Then...
-  Yes?
Until the sagol is defrosted,
- can I take a shower?
-  Sure. Go ahead.
(Of course.)
(He chose to take a shower as the last resort.)
(The heat won't go away.)
(It's so hot.)
(It's extremely hot.)
(I can't stand it any more.)
(He puts the bag of sagol on his belly.)
I'm feeling so hot.
(He drinks soda to cool his throat.)
(After he finishes the soda,)
(he throws the bottle away.)
I'm starting to feel cool.
(The frozen sagol starts to cool his body down.)
(Wriggling)
(He puts the bag on his back.)
(Oh, yes.)
(What's he doing?)
That's good. That's a good idea.
Did you take a shower?
Yes, I did. It's hot.
(I'm still feeling hot even after a shower.)
Get some cool breeze.
- It doesn't make a big difference.
-  I'll turn the fan.
Thank you.
That's too strong.
(He feels tired.)
(The fan is of no help at all.)
- This is too much.
-  What a shame.
I bought an air conditioner to make you feel at home.
Will it be set up while I'm staying here?
I'll do my best to make that happen.
I'm sure that orders are really backed up.
So many people buy an air conditioner.
I'm hungry, though.
Gosh.
Let's heat up the sagol.
- Let's go.
-  Okay.
I'm hungry.
It feels like I'm in my house.
My table is here.
I'm glad you have a dining table now.
Me, too. It's good to have a guest.
He tied this so tightly.
Do you have scissors?
I'll heat up the instant rice.
- Okay.
-  I'll heat it up.
- I'll heat up the sagol.
-  Okay.
If I hadn't moved out, I wouldn't have remembered this.
(He's cutting the bag with a knife.)
I can't believe I'm doing this.
What am I doing?
- Hold on.
-  It works.
It looks like I'm cutting a watermelon.
It's like shaved ice made with sagol soup.
Who's calling you? Is it a girl?
Hello?
Oh, hello.
(To whom is he talking so nicely?)
You can set it up now?
Really?
They'll set up the air conditioner now?
- We don't have to go to a motel?
-  That's right.
Thank you.
- He's coming.
-  At this hour?
Yes, he said he's coming.
That's really nice of him.
This is for you.
Can I just eat it as it is?
I think we can warm it in the microwave.
- Are you going to put it in there?
-  Let's boil it in here.
- That's a good idea.
-  Yes.
It'll be done quickly.
You take care of me better than my mum.
It's so nice to have someone in my house.
- You should eat well.
-  Okay.
I know how it feels because...
I'm not so different from you.
- Really?
-  But there is...
something I learned.
I eat fruits no matter what.
I'm trying to eat fruits more often.
Eating fruits makes a big difference.
- Let's sit side by side.
-  Okay.
- Isn't nice to have a dining table?
-  It's so good.
- It's good, but...
-  Yes.
I was criticised so much because of this.
I read those comments, too, as I check them all the time.
- Did you?
-  Of course.
- Someone said, "Hyun Moo is cool."
-  Right.
I hadn't read a good comment like that...
in two years.
At least, you got good comments. I'm happy for you.
I felt bad for you.
I said I didn't need the table.
Why would they criticise you?
When you were criticised for selling my sketch,
I read some comments about you saying,
"He's always like that. I don't even want to see his face."
(They don't even want to see his face?)
I thought you had done so much wrong.
They said, "He's always like that."
I have a bad image.
Harsh comments hurt your feelings at first.
When I read harsh comments about me for the first time,
I couldn't go outside.
Why?
I thought everyone hated me.
Think about it.
I get hurt easily, too.
- But it's better than no comment.
-  I see.
- It's true.
-  You're right.
- It's the same for my webtoon.
-  Of course.
Actually,
I overcame it by getting used to it.
I read harsh comments more often.
There are...
constructive criticisms and meaningless ones.
- There are logical criticisms...
-  Yes.
that explain why my behaviours or words cause an issue.
- They really hurt my feelings.
-  I understand.
- But I can accept them.
-  I know how it feels.
That's right.
There are a few of them.
The rest are all meaningless. "I hate you."
"I don't want to see your face." "Go away."
"You're despicable." They have no reasonable ground.
- What can I do about it?
-  I...
I can't just tell them, "I'm actually adorable."
You wouldn't understand if you haven't read harsh comments.
When you read one for the first time,
it feels like everyone hates you.
Kian84 must feel like he's lost everything.
I wanted to let him know that he hasn't.
I managed to overcome it by myself.
It's like growing pains. It happens a lot.
- I think it's done.
-  It looks delicious.
- Indeed. Shall we eat now?
-  Let's eat.
It looks amazing.
(It's steaming.)
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Be careful.
I should put it away.
(It's too hot.)
Do you have salt?
I don't have salt at home.
- What about chilli pepper powder?
-  I don't have it.
- Do you not have pepper, either?
-  No.
- Let's eat it as it is.
-  Okay.
(He's forced to have a low sodium diet.)
This is real sagol.
It'll be good for our bodies.
(He adds a bowl of warm rice to it.)
(This is nice.)
(You can't leave out aged kimchi.)
- How is it?
-  It's delicious.
You'll thank me later. You have to eat this kind of food.
Samgyetang, fish...
(It's hard to eat well when you live alone.)
and gomtang...
You have to eat these kinds of food.
It's delicious.
(The warmth of the soup spreads though their bodies.)
- It's good.
-  It is, isn't it?
It's very good.
(They're fighting heat with heat.)
This is nice.
Why did I take a shower? We're drenched in sweat.
(They're practically at a sauna.)
That's nice.
(He drinks up his bowl of soup.)
Thank you for the food.
I had good food, thanks to you.
This is the first time I've had sagol this year.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I'm full.
Let me help.
(They do the dishes right away.)
(He sweats profusely after the meal.)
(The tissue sticks to his face.)
(This is Kian84's simple way of doing the dishes.)
(He fills the bowl with water...)
(and dumps it out.)
(What?)
Are you done?
Was my bowl washed like this?
Yes, I washed it like that earlier.
Are you serious?
I don't believe you.
(He washes the dishes again.)
(He's still sweating.)
Hyun Moo, are you trying to look good on TV?
I don't want people to criticise me.
Actually, it's not because of what people think of me.
I like doing the dishes.
You like doing the dishes?
I realised something after being on this show.
I know what people like...
and what they don't. I become conscious of that.
I also started wondering why Hyun Moo was doing the dishes...
and why he keeps giving me food.
I kept thinking about it.
I don't know why.
I was becoming paranoid, thinking there's an ulterior motive.
Turn the fan on at least.
That feels cool.
It's very hot today.
It's too hot.
Not even my mum does the dishes.
Are you sure you like doing the dishes?
Yes, I do. Why?
That's why I don't cook. I can't leave dirty dishes around.
(He sweats profusely with every step.)
It's hot.
That was a nice meal.
Should we have some peaches?
Let's eat it whole.
(Let's just eat it whole.)
(Hyun Moo brought the peaches.)
(He bites into the peach.)
- It's good, isn't it?
-  Yes, it is.
How's it so hard?
It used to be harder.
- It's softer now.
-  It is?
Yes, I left it out for too long.
(How will they survive the hot and humid night?)
(What is Gook Ju doing in the heat?)
She lives in a nice neighbourhood.
(She's visiting someone.)
You can have everything delivered if you live in this area.
It's a flat.
(Who lives here?)
I wonder if she's cleaning.
All she has to prepare is food.
(She has nothing to eat at home, but she's cleaning.)
(She wipes the table with a wet wipe.)
I'll try to look like a model.
(She shakes her head side to side.)
Hi.
I'm Model Lee Gook Ju.
(She tries to look sexy by blowing wind in her hair.)
The weather is too hot.
(She rushes out.)
(This is Gook Ju's first time visiting Hye Jin's home.)
Hi, it's so cool in here.
It's so cool.
Wear these.
- These?
-  Yes, I left them out for you.
My feet are sweaty. Is it okay if the slippers smell?
It's okay. I'll throw them out.
Wow.
When I first met her,
I had a feeling we'd get along.
(She saw Hye Jin order food early in the morning.)
I live on the 11th floor.
I can tell when the food is almost here.
I wait outside.
I open the door when I think the food is at my doorstep.
This would go well with soju.
She's just like me.
It's there when I open the door.
I don't easily open up to other people.
But I asked for her number right away.
I wanted to get to know her better.
Thankfully, she invited me over.
I want to talk with her today...
and get to know her better.
What's this?
I brought a gift.
It's pretty heavy.
Last time, I saw you...
drink wine out of a packet.
- I've tried soju out of a packet.
-  I didn't know that existed.
- It's fills one glass?
-  One glass?
This is way better than that.
- Way better?
-  Yes.
It has more class and is made with more sincerity.
It's much better.
Take a look at it.
What's this?
Is it snake wine?
Does it have a snake in it?
Is that what you wanted?
It's bokbunja ju.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I used to make a lot of it.
I gave it out to the Rainbow Club members.
Really?
I wanted to give you a bottle as well.
(She makes a face as she adds the bokbunja.)
(She pours the alcohol in it.)
(She mixes the berries with alcohol to make bokbunja ju.)
Is that enough?
(Let's try it.)
She's trying it right away.
(She's excited to try the wine.)
- You couldn't wait?
-  It's alcohol.
Yes, it is.
- I drink every day.
-  It's really alcohol.
You made this?
(She lets out a sound of satisfaction.)
It's strong.
Yes, it is.
- It's strong.
-  Do you know how I felt?
It reminded me of cognac.
It warmed my chest up.
Me, too.
I wonder if all the other members are drinking it.
- It's only 2:30 in the afternoon.
-  This feels weird.
It made my heart race.
I feel like I got an IV with wine.
I feel like it's still flowing in me.
Let's have it chilled.
- Okay, put it in the refrigerator.
-  It'll be better chilled.
- Wow.
-  What is it?
It's so empty.
What's this? It's a huge disappointment.
I have to go grocery shopping.
This is it.
This is white wine.
Stop that.
I'll give you a few when you go home.
I was in Hong Kong for vacation...
Come on.
You froze your food waste again.
It's because I knew you were coming.
You should've thrown it out, not freeze it.
Now my hands are sticky.
I cleaned the whole place for you.
But that trash is from this morning.
I didn't know you'd open my freezer.
- I open everything.
-  Wait.
Wait a second.
I see a bike.
I only go in there to do the laundry.
I'm going to take a thorough look around.
(Gook Ju checks every corner of the flat.)
This is a model's room.
This is embarrassing. I don't have much.
(Top Model Hye Jin's room is simpler than we expected.)
You're tall.
- Your closet is longer than most.
-  How did you know?
- I customised the closet.
-  I could tell.
Normal people don't need this.
We don't need taller closets.
Look at this.
Isn't this a weightlifter?
(She's holding strong on to a bar.)
I've never seen anyone say that.
It looks like the weights should be attached to the bar.
You look like a weightlifter at the Olympics.
That's cool.
I'll show you what it is.
(It's the cover of a fashion magazine.)
You're on the cover of a magazine. I want to be on one, too.
I was on the cover of a magazine once.
I want to try something like this.
How did you look?
- Me?
-  Yes.
I looked strong and powerful.
I have my poses.
I like biting my finger.
You did that for the cover of a magazine?
(This is what she did.)
- It was just my face.
-  Just your face?
Not many people get to do that.
It's something only top celebrities can do.
Here it is.
The dress is open at the back.
You're sitting on a chair.
You have your arms laying on the armrest.
This makes your legs look short.
I'll show you how to sit.
I need to learn this.
This is how you were sitting.
This is how models sit.
We sit at the edge of the chair.
Sit at the edge.
- I sat comfortably in the chair.
-  First, sit at the edge.
Lean sideways and make an S shape with your body.
- I see.
-  Then stretch your legs.
Stretch those as far as you can.
You can stretch them like this.
You want to look like this.
You look uncomfortable.
You won't look good in the pictures if you're comfortable.
You could sit on the other side.
This is something people were curious about.
You want to sit like this even when taking selfies.
Like this.
(This is how you sit in a chair.)
Wow.
My old pictures are mixed with recent ones.
- You're lying down, aren't you?
-  How did you know?
(She is riding a bike while lying on the floor.)
You know how to make fashion look funny.
You have a keen eye.
I used to draw.
My dream was to become a fashion designer.
- Objet...
-  Objet designs?
That time, I used to buy...
three magazines like this every month.
I put all of them in my scrapbook.
I couldn't study fashion because my grades weren't good.
(They both love fashion.)
I should've studied. Gosh, this...
(She looks at a different magazine.)
(She looks scary.)
Wait... This...
I think it's 1:55pm.
- I think it's cute.
-  I was very angry at the time.
I lived abroad then. I was an angry kid.
I can see the anger in your eyes.
I was an angry girl.
(She exuded her anger.)
Think about it.
If comedians did this, it'd be too funny.
What do you mean? You always made fun of us.
Jang Do Yeon and Park Na Rae did that.
Did you call me?
I saw that pose before.
(I saw that pose before.)
This is it.
(They started to laugh out loud.)
(We found it.)
Jang Do Yeon Jang Do Yeon
It's because models always do the same pose.
What else can we do?
First we do the standard poses. Later,
we face forward, turn around and do a bunch of things.
When the photographer asks for something different...
- I see.
-  Are you happy?
My stomach.
I think I drank too much.
My stomach hurts.
(The hangover pose)
- This is what that is.
-  Yes.
- Gosh, you were so young.
-  I was.
Look at the clothes. It's crazy.
Gosh. That's Gang Dong Won. That's awesome.
(Gang Dong Won when he was a model)
Gosh.
That's awesome. Look at his eyes.
(This is...)
(Zo In Sung, Gook Ju's ideal man.)
I can't believe it.
Choose either Zo In Sung or Gang Dong Won. On 1, 2, 3.
(She blanks out.)
Zo In Sung or Kang Dong Won. On 1, 2, 3.
(Zo In Sung versus Gang Dong Won)
I just want to see if we like the same type or not.
- This is hard.
-  I know.
- It's too hard.
-  What shall we do?
It's hard because...
- they're both perfect.
-  Wait.
- I'll download the app.
-  Is there an app for this?
You haven't tried it yet?
- Gosh.
-  I only tried it on the show.
- Well...
-  Why do you do it by yourself?
- This is really interesting.
-  Really?
I play this three times before I go to sleep.
They appear in your dreams, seriously.
- Why do you do this?
-  Wait.
Do they really appear in your dreams?
Ideal men type...
- Ideal Actor World Cup.
-  Okay.
Lee Jong Hyun versus Kim Woo Bin.
Okay, it's Lee Jong Hyun versus Kim Woo Bin.
On a hot day, a man brings you a cold drink.
He takes a sip and passes it to you.
Why does he have to sip it first?
It's almost like a kiss.
One, two, three.
- Kim Woo Bin.
-  Kim Woo Bin, let's go.
We have the same taste.
Kim Ji Seok versus Lee Jang Woo.
- One, two, three.
-  Wait.
(Wait)
(She pretended not to be interested, but now she's into it.)
- Think about it.
-  Wait.
- This is quite nerve-racking.
-  It's really hot right now.
You're sweating.
- All of a sudden, wind is blowing.
-  Okay.
You turn around. A man is fanning you and smiling at you.
Who do you want it to be?
Kim Ji Seok or Lee Jang Woo. One, two, three.
(Kim Ji Seok versus Lee Jang Woo)
- Kim Ji Seok.
-  Okay, let's go.
We have the same taste.
This is getting worse.
- Okay, next.
-  Here it is.
- Joo Won versus Kwon Yul.
-  Joo Won.
Joo Won? I see.
Well, I...
So he's your type.
No. I usually don't like people with strong features.
When I was filming "Fashion King"...
I spent much time with Joo Won.
In the movie,
- he wears a T-shirt with me on it.
-  I see.
Well... I shouldn't say this on TV.
Why not? You keep doing this.
He's going to find out how I thought of him then.
You shouldn't hide it. You have to say it.
Did you like him wearing a T-shirt with you on it?
My heart was going to burst.
Like when you drank bokbunja ju before?
My heart was pounding.
I saw him for the first time then.
It was like when I saw a handsome actor.
I was like, "Who's this guy?"
(I thought my heart was going to stop.)
I think Joo Won is number one right now.
Kim Ji Seok versus Lee Je Hoon.
This is unfair for me.
You won't be able to choose anyone in the finals.
- Why am I so torn?
-  You're...
meeting him at the airport to go on a trip secretly.
He appears with a mask and a cap on.
- You're so funny.
-  You'd say, "Hey, you're here."
He whispers in your ears,
"Let's meet at the duty-free shop later."
Why meet at a duty-free shop?
- Why not on the plane?
-  You have to...
buy a bottle of wine.
Imagine him whispering in your ears.
Kim Ji Seok goes...
- well with this situation.
-  Okay, Kim Ji Seok.
- What's all this?
-  Okay, it's the finals.
(Kim Ji Seok versus Joo Won)
Without wearing a shirt.
- A girl not wearing a shirt?
-  No, a man.
Shirtless like this.
(He's cooking for you and showing off his muscles.)
He's cooking like this.
"It'll be done soon."
Who would you choose?
Joo Won. She picked Joo Won.
It was Joo Won from the beginning.
Gosh, what am I going to do?
- Shall I save his picture?
-  What?
- You can save it.
-  Don't do it.
I can save this picture. I'll send it to you.
- Don't do it.
-  Shall I send it to you?
- No, it's okay. I'm embarrassed.
-  Why?
Girls talk about boys when we get together.
We talk about the people we're interested in.
We talk about handsome guys we saw.
It doesn't matter if you're a comedian or a model.
It's the topic girls talk about when we get together.
We got along great and we had fun.
I think I'll treat her as my big sister.
(We're friends forever.)
- You saw them all.
-  Yes.
Who's your favourite?
- There's one guy.
-  Who is it?
- Maybe I should learn Chinese.
-  What are you saying?
Do you know Darren Wang?
No. That's his name?
- You don't know him?
-  Is he...
Chinese? It that his name?
There was a movie that was recommended.
- It's called "Our Times".
-  Okay.
He's so charming in the movie.
- Darren Wang is?
-  Yes, I'll show you.
Do we have the same TV?
Wait, I'll turn it on.
(I'll show you the movie he's in.)
(Our Times)
- Did you eat yet?
-  No.
I thought about sundaeguk on the way here.
- Come on.
-  Sundaeguk.
(Hye Jin eating sundaeguk in the morning...)
(left a deep impression on Gook Ju.)
- I actually drank last night.
-  I see.
- We can eat while watching TV.
-  Sundaeguk would be good then.
I just have to call my favourite place.
Please bring two from Cheongdam-dong.
Please bring 1 kkakdugi and 1 sliced radish.
Okay. Would you like to add a bowl of rice?
A bowl of rice should come with it for free.
I need to check.
- I know for sure.
-  Thank you.
(I finally get to eat it.)
(It's time to meet Darren Wang.)
After I watched this,
I wanted to experience an innocent love again.
- You really enjoyed this movie.
-  Yes.
Look. It's the cafeteria.
The noodles.
I can play that role.
(Gook Ju would've played that role if the movie was Korean.)
I want jjamppong all of a sudden.
But there wasn't anything about jjamppong in the movie.
I feel like having jjamppong.
(I'm craving it.)
- Let's order it.
-  What?
- Pause the movie.
-  How will you eat it?
Of course, I can.
- All right. Let's order.
-  Okay.
Jjamppong.
You said jjamppong first, not me.
Yes, I get to eat jjamppong and sundaeguk.
I should wait for sundaeguk while waiting for jjamppong.
I want one jjamppong...
and a jjajangmyeon.
I told you, you're greedy.
(She's my type.)
We have to order jjajangmyeon.
You mentioned jjamppong first.
- The two shouldn't arrive together.
-  Why not?
- Then...
-  One should come first.
It they arrive at once, I can't eat a lot.
No worries. We can eat.
Let's see what kind of other food is hidden.
What are we watching? Darren Whang or the food?
(Darren Wang appears finally.)
He's handsome.
He is handsome.
It's as if he's looking at me.
I'll say this when I meet him.
- What does it mean?
-  What's your phone number?
You're funny.
(Only those who are prepared gets handsome men.)
- I really like him these days.
-  Who?
(I really like him these days.)
I even wrote down his blog address.
Xiumin.
(Xiumin of EXO)
From here, you're different from me.
- He's just so cute.
-  He's cute.
(They talk freely about boys now that they're close.)
Look at you.
- You look so happy.
-  Well...
You look the happiest since I came here.
(They're immersed in the movie.)
- Is it going to be sundaeguk?
-  No.
I think it's Chinese food.
(Which one arrived first?)
- Yes?
-  What is it, Hye Jin?
Our Chinese food arrived. As usual, they're fast.
We have to eat the noodles first.
(It looks delicious.)
- Yes.
-  Oh, no.
I'm so happy.
Let's eat.
I can't spill.
I'm in trouble.
If you don't mind the calories, you won't gain weight.
(If you're happy with your food, you won't gain weight.)
(She's getting the remaining sauce with the noodles.)
Wow, Hye Jin.
You're not wasting any of it.
You're so frugal.
- Well...
-  That's smart.
There isn't enough sauce.
(It looks delicious.)
Relax and eat today.
(She eats with her mouth.)
He's so handsome.
Oh, my goodness.
- He has a very nice smile.
-  Right.
(It feels we're in a paradise.)
(Sighing)
Are you treating your hangover?
I don't need to apply lip gloss.
(Because the soup is oily.)
(She's not even listening.)
You're not even listening.
You're just waiting for the doorbell to ring.
It's so obvious.
- Sorry.
-  I really...
Right?
I'm still talking.
You're so eager to get the door.
(The sundaeguk comes first.)
The door is open.
Hold on, Darren Wang.
(Goodness)
He's looking at me.
Hye Jin...
I can't set the table.
- Why not?
-  He's staring at me.
- Gosh.
-  I'm going insane.
He's looking over there.
Hello, Darren.
Gosh.
(Hye Jin opens the sundaeguk roughly.)
You're strong.
You have to pierce it.
- We need this.
-  Right.
(They start eating with the TV paused.)
This is great.
- Your hangover will get better.
-  Right.
I drank too much last night.
How late were you out?
- Until 3:30am.
-  Really?
(Gook Ju drank until 3:30am.)
We started drinking at 11pm.
You started late.
Do you know how much meat the five of us ate?
We ate 850 dollars' worth of meat.
There must have been guys there.
They were all guys except for me.
Really?
No way.
- Really?
-  You want to see the photos?
What's your secret?
I'm not their type.
They're comfortable with me.
I see.
I'm not threatening.
They just see me as a good friend.
- I must be threatening.
-  I guess.
I act like a mother to them.
- Motherly?
-  Then all of a sudden,
I act like a real woman.
You go from being motherly to being ladylike?
Have you ever dated anyone like that?
- Yes.
-  Really?
It never happens right away.
When I show my interest,
- the guys tend to back off.
-  Right.
You become friends.
Later on, they say,
"I kept thinking about you."
- "You're a really good woman."
-  I see.
You were always...
friends before dating, right?
I'd do anything for the man I love.
That's just like me.
When people talk about relationships,
I disagree with the saying that...
people who give it their all tend to regret it less.
I think that's nonsense.
I'm serious.
It's a lot more difficult for the person who gives more.
- It's more difficult.
-  It's more painful.
It's more painful, too.
I always remember the gifts I gave.
(I always remember the gifts I gave.)
I calculate the cost.
I drove my ex-boyfriends around a lot.
That's a given.
- You did that, too?
-  Of course.
(They're bitter.)
I've done everything men usually do for women.
I picked them up...
- and paid for drinks and meals.
-  You waited for them.
I prepared special events for them...
- You're just like me.
-  with friends.
(We're the same.)
When shopping, I spend more on my boyfriend...
than on myself.
During those times,
- You rationalise.
-  Right.
"I'm buying myself something, too."
"I'm not just buying him things."
I rationalise it.
My feelings are sincere.
I'm sincere.
(They're so alike.)
The sundaeguk is delicious.
There's not enough sundae.
Do you want some of mine? I like the other stuff.
- Really?
-  Yes.
(Single women sharing sundaeguk)
Dating is...
really exhausting.
Are they here?
(Kian84's house is 35C.)
(He rushes over.)
Yes?
That was quick.
(Are they here?)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Thank you for coming so late.
- I'm sorry.
-  Sorry for arriving late.
- I didn't think you'd arrive.
-  Sorry.
How long will it take?
Around an hour and a half.
- An hour and a half.
-  Really?
- Kian84.
-  Yes?
Can we please leave?
- You want to go out?
-  I'm dying.
Can you call me 10 minutes before you're done?
- I'll come home.
-  All right.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
- All right.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
Put these slippers on, Hyun Moo.
- Can I borrow them?
-  Here they are.
All right.
(They look like twins.)
It's so cool.
Is it?
If the air conditioner hadn't come,
we could've slept here in a tent.
It's cool out here.
It's cool, but how can we sleep here?
Your house is the hottest place.
(Your house is the hottest place.)
(Neighbourhood commercial area)
- Let's go.
-  Let's go to the arcade.
It's been a while since I've gone to those places.
It's like going out after midterms.
(They're the excited slipper brothers.)
Wearing slippers like this.
Did you go to arcades a lot?
That's why I had to retake my college admission test.
It was because of football games.
You had to reapply because of football video games?
I entered a tournament and failed to get into college.
(Arcade)
(Let's battle.)
(There can only be one winner at the arcade.)
(I'm the Tekken master.)
(Expert hand movements)
(He slides over...)
(and counterpunches.)
(He wins.)
(Despite Hyun Moo's attacks,)
(he wins again.)
(Chuckling)
(In an instant, Hyun Moo loses three times.)
(I win.)
Don't cry, Hyun Moo.
You're no match for me.
(He becomes enraged.)
(He furiously pushes any buttons.)
(Hyun Moo's rage...)
(catches the expert off guard.)
What's going on?
(Here I come.)
What's this?
That's it.
Destroy him.
(Destroy him.)
He's good.
(I don't know what's happening either.)
Destroy him.
That's it.
(Is he fighting with his facial expressions?)
What's this?
(Hyun Moo beats Kian84.)
(He's newbie who got lucky.)
Wow.
(The expert is bitter.)
(They're giving it everything they have.)
I can't punch.
(When Hyun Moo shakes his leg,)
(his character kicks.)
What's this?
I was completely winning at first.
Then I went easy on him and lost a round.
I thought I should let him win a round.
He's older and went to the arcade with me.
I didn't want to go overboard.
So I let him win.
(After the battle, they head upstairs.)
It's so cool in here.
Each floor is great.
(Hyun Moo and Kian84 head to a karaoke.)
Let's sing for an hour.
- All right.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  It's so cool.
This is a room for two.
It's been a while since I've been to a karaoke.
What songs do you like? Ballads?
I like ballads.
Really?
When it's just guys, we always sing ballads.
- I sing ballads, too.
-  Right.
When there are women, you sing idol songs...
- to liven up the mood, right?
-  Right.
We're all about the emotion though.
Men love Cho Jang Hyuk.
In my generation, it was Yarn and Yada.
I also like Buzz.
Buzz? How about Kim Sung Myun from K2?
We used to sing those songs during the entire hour.
That's just like me.
(Kian84's first song)
This song is difficult.
The person with the higher score...
(The winner gets to sleep in the living room.)
- sleeps in the living room.
-  In the living room?
The loser has to sleep in the hot bedroom.
(He got startled.)
(He misses a beat.)
(Just a person like me)
I won.
(It's impossible to recognise the original song.)
That's incredible.
(He shakes his foot in preparation for the high note.)
What's this?
Here comes the climax.
(He's shaking his foot to sing the high notes.)
(I reveal myself)
(Unintentionally)
(He's lost it.)
(You don't know how much I want to sleep in peace.)
I'll sing something else. It's too difficult.
I used to be able to hit the high notes.
- You have no sense of rhythm.
-  Right.
It's been a while since I sang.
- You were completely off beat.
-  Right.
Your voice is great though.
I'm relaxed because you started off like that.
- Really?
-  It won't matter how I sing.
- It was that bad?
-  You've got a serious issue.
Really?
I'll sing "Eyes, Nose, Lips".
That's a tough one.
(Don't say sorry)
(It makes me feel pitiful)
(The listener feels out of breath.)
(I'm okay)
(Your eyes, nose and lips)
(He adds soul to his voice.)
(He throws himself into the song with his eyes, nose and lips.)
(You have to close your eyes while singing RnB.)
(He's grooving to the music)
(He's completely full of himself.)
Hold on.
Hold on. What's going on?
I was going to add the next song to the playlist.
- I pushed the wrong button.
-  That's so rude.
- It was an accident.
-  I was doing really well.
- I made a mistake.
-  I get 100 points then.
I pushed the wrong button by accident.
- I cancelled it.
-  I got 100 points.
- What?
No, you have to start over.
(My song was flawless.)
Is this your way of winning?
No.
Next.
(Now it's Kian84's turn.)
It's been a while since I sang this.
I'll give it a go.
- Here I go.
-  Applause.
(Taesaja in the house)
("Way" by Taesaja was released in 1997.)
You're a good rapper.
(You have to be in your 30s to know this song.)
(The breathless rapping is the key point of the song.)
(He starts singing after the rap.)
(He can't catch his breath.)
(I live in the hottest house in the world.)
(So I'll have refreshing dreams.)
(He practised his vibe since 1997.)
(I say)
(Yes)
That was your best song so far.
- Was it all right?
-  It was the best so far.
You got 100 points.
(He scored 100 points.)
(He started laughing out loud.)
- I'm in trouble.
-  You just need to sing loudly.
Then...
(This song isn't sung when it's all just men.)
It's "Cheer Up".
(In order to sleep in a cool room,)
(he starts off with a cute dance.)
(Kian84 ignores him while searching for his next song.)
(It's embarrassing.)
(Cheer up, baby)
(He's a childishly cheerful 40-year-old.)
(Men can't lose a wager.)
(I'll like myself better that way.)
(Even if I lose, I'll act like I don't care.)
(As if nothing matters)
(He's twice as old as Twice.)
(However, he forgets his age and sings his heart out.)
(Did you see that?)
That was great.
You did great, Hyun Moo.
- Look.
-  What's that?
The machine is weird.
This is your neighbourhood.
Hold on.
(Kian84 changes things up for his next move.)
(He sings about men's life.)
A high note is coming up.
(No one knows what will come next)
(It's no fun if you win easily)
(His low voice eases suffering.)
(While he sings about life's struggles,)
(Hyun Moo bursts out laughing.)
(Screaming)
(It ends with shouts and laughter.)
(Men love emotional ballads.)
(When you close your eyes,)
(you remember your past lovers.)
(How did the story of my life become a song?)
(Today,)
(he sings in sorrow while in slippers.)
(They're the stars of a romance movie.)
(Singing about love in spite of a clenched throat)
(He keeps looking for his next song.)
It's been so long since I've sung at a karaoke.
- A ballad?
-  What's the song I always sing?
What's the song I always sing?
Did the power go out?
This has never happened before.
(The power went out at the karaoke.)
Is it because of the air conditioner?
They must have used too much electricity.
The other rooms are dark, too.
- Let's go.
-  We can't sing without electricity.
That's too bad. I wanted to sing one more.
- That was fun.
-  I had fun, too.
It's so dark.
(It's now late.)
(They return home, exhausted from having too much fun.)
Let's see.
Look.
(The air conditioner was installed.)
I should've done this a long time ago.
Why was I only using the fan for so long?
You have an air conditioner now.
What a beautiful sound.
(This sound will relieve the heat.)
The air conditioner is on.
It's so powerful.
I'll sleep standing up.
I should've bought an air conditioner a long time ago.
- This is so great.
-  It's really cool.
- It's great.
-  You know I won, right?
- All right.
-  All right.
Go sleep inside.
- Right now?
-  Hurry up.
Do I have to go in?
It's not cool inside, right?
It's hot in here.
It's not cool.
The floor won't be sticky any more.
I'll spread the blankets for you.
Is that new?
It's for you.
Really? Thank you. That's new.
I'll use an old one.
It's brand new.
(That's very thoughtful of you.)
- Is this all you need?
-  That's all I need.
What's that?
- Is that a comforter?
-  Is this a sheet?
(Is this a sheet?)
You want me to use this as a blanket?
- It's a sheet.
-  This is a bed sheet.
- I thought it was a blanket.
-  Should I slide inside?
Is that a sleeping bag?
- Why did I get this?
-  What's this?
You ordered the wrong thing.
Let's just flip it over.
- Just turn it over.
-  Why do you keep flipping things?
This works.
It's not bad.
Lie down here?
Shouldn't you return it?
Just use it.
It's still a piece of fabric.
- It's too much work to return it.
-  All right.
- You can use that.
-  I don't need it.
You only have a thick blanket.
I got this for you.
- It's for you.
-  Really?
It's new.
I bought it since you were coming over.
- Lay down on it.
-  I'm like your grandfather.
I'll get you a pillow.
Here you go.
Are you going to sleep?
Do you want to drink?
- You want to drink?
-  Let's drink.
Let's have a beer.
- A beer?
-  Yes.
I snore after I drink beer.
- You snore?
-  Yes.
Let's not drink, then.
Don't drink.
Why don't you go inside?
I'm going to bed a little later.
- Just sleep here.
-  What?
Let's sleep together.
- I bought all of that.
-  Just sleep here.
How can I sleep next to a man?
- It's hot.
-  Right.
Sleeping on the floor is best.
Goodness.
- This is great.
-  Seriously.
(He starts shifting position.)
Do you want to watch a movie?
- A movie?
-  I can't sleep.
All right.
(They turn the TV on.)
- Like this.
-  Why is that on TV...
when the two of us are alone?
Lie down.
- Kian84.
-  What?
I'll just sit up.
That's great.
(They found a new way to overcome the hot night.)
Wow.
It's the original imported version.
(Is the air conditioner off? It's getting hot again.)
- Let's watch something else.
-  All right.
You're shy.
(They change the channel.)
(Again?)
- Sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
-  Right.
Why are they selling so much underwear?
It must sell well.
I wish they sold my comic books on TV.
That's amazing.
(Goodness)
I keep watching even though I have no intention of buying.
- Let's watch something else.
-  Why?
Is this fun?
- Don't you like it?
-  Why are you watching this?
You're not going to buy it.
It's Friday after all.
There's nothing to watch.
Since I live alone,
it's been a while...
since I opened up to someone.
It's been a while since I've lied down and chatted with someone.
It felt really strange.
When I was younger,
we used to lie around like that...
when relatives came over to visit.
It reminded me of that.
There's Dong Hyun.
Dong Hyun threw a punch.
That's it.
(He's immersed in Dong Hyun's match.)
That's right.
Are you close friends?
- We're close.
-  Really?
I was in a Muay Thai match before.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I used to go to the gym for two months.
They wanted me to compete.
They said I would do well.
I agreed.
My opponent looked easy.
I thought I'd win easily.
But he was on another level.
I got beaten up.
I started working hard on my comics then.
- You gave up Muay Thai?
-  Yes.
(It's been an amazing day due to the heat.)
It's so cool.
- It's best at home.
-  Well...
We bought a lot. I can stay for a few days, Hye Jin.
Right?
(The abundance of food makes her happy.)
I'll make you carbonara tteokbokki.
- Carbonara?
-  Yes.
I don't have any decent cooking utensils.
Is this okay?
The mushrooms alone won't fit in that.
Are you joking?
You can tell that I live alone, right?
That's for frying a single egg.
- Are you kidding?
-  The biggest pan...
- I have is this one.
-  You have one.
- I only have this.
-  That can work.
I only have a frying pan.
That's fine.
I'm excited.
- I'll begin.
-  All right.
(She starts to cook like an expert.)
When do you add the cream?
When the rice cake is cooked,
add milk and cheese.
You add milk and cheese instead of cream?
(She's a great cook who only needs milk.)
I'll get the milk.
(A cheap yet elegant dish for Hye Jin)
We can add the milk now.
(She adds a generous amount of milk.)
- Isn't that too much?
-  It'll reduce.
- Isn't the colour great?
-  It's great.
- It looks like cream sauce.
-  Right.
My mouth is watering.
You already lost.
That's no joke.
It's carbonara and bokbunja ju.
This is seriously no joke.
(Hye Jin is preparing ramyeon to go with it.)
We need some soup.
I like to add garlic.
(Wow)
(Hye Jin only adds two-thirds of the noodles.)
(Gook Ju is unaware while she tastes the tteokbokki.)
Yum.
I'll add half of the soup base.
(She only adds half to reduce sodium intake.)
Wow.
- Milk makes you bloat less.
-  That's right.
- If you eat salty food...
-  You'll get bloated.
I'll add the cheese, too.
(Gook Ju keeps eating while the ramyeon cooks.)
(Yum)
(They're both standing while they eat.)
- Yum.
-  It's good.
(They're able to communicate without any words.)
This is amazing.
Why did you only use half of the noodles?
No, it's two-thirds.
Why didn't you add all of it?
I don't understand you, Hye Jin.
- How annoying.
-  Let's go.
Why didn't you cook it all?
No wonder the portion looked too small.
(The model's ramyeon is lacking.)
(The expert cook's tteokbokki is generous.)
- This is great.
-  I'll start with the ramyeon.
We're supposed to share that.
- What?
-  It's for both of us.
You didn't even cook everything.
I can finish it in two bites.
I hate sharing noodles.
Why?
It's never enough.
- That's good.
-  No, it isn't.
I like it when the noodles hit my cheek as I slurp them.
- Like this?
-  Of course.
(She slurps angrily.)
It's really good.
(They're happily eating together.)
(She drinks milk because the ramyeon is spicy.)
You're a great cook.
You could open a restaurant.
You could charge 35 dollars in Cheongdam-dong.
(She's satisfied with the food.)
(They're happy just eating.)
Eating this...
makes me think of sundaeguk.
What's with you? Go home.
When are you leaving? It's past 10pm.
I like it here.
The sofa fits me perfectly.
I look better in this house than you do.
(They finally finish eating.)
(She's tired.)
(She's exhausted from eating all day.)
There's a difference between us.
- What?
-  We're both full.
But you moved over there.
I'm still in the same spot.
That's why we look different.
You have to move after eating.
Not yet.
- Not yet?
-  No.
You need something in common to get along with someone.
As I get older, it isn't easy...
to find a friend I get along with.
I relieved a lot of stress today. It was great.
I hope we can meet often to eat and chat together.
It's the first time...
anyone has come to hang out with me.
It's the first time after I moved here.
Gook Ju threw a rock...
into my placid life.
I'll probably be lonely for a while.
This is nice. After 30 minutes,
let's order some eel.
I digested the tteokbokki already.
Aren't you leaving?
I really like it here.
This is fun.
(It's so fun here.)
I want to eat more, Hye Jin.
(It was a busy and fun day.)
(Chae A is at a gym in Ilsan.)
Is this it?
(Chae A is very much excited.)
(Agile)
Hello.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- Are you the director?
-  Yes.
- Yes.
-  Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
-  Yes.
I'm going to be in a movie.
I'm playing a special agent.
Since I'm a special agent,
I have to do action scenes.
It's my first day learning martial arts at the action school.
I want the action scenes to be realistic.
The genre of the film is action comedy.
- But the action...
-  I want it to be realistic.
- I want it to be really realistic.
-  Right.
I play a detective, so I want it to be great.
- Let's have a plan.
-  All right.
- We'll practise according to that.
-  Right.
Please follow along.
I'll do my best.
- Let's start with kicks.
-  All right.
(Actor who will appear with Chae A in the action scene)
(He demonstrates the kick first.)
Director?
(He shows quickness.)
(His kick is powerful.)
I'm scared.
- Get ready.
-  All right.
It needs to be powerful so you'd need to shout.
(Will Chae A do well?)
That's it.
(She turns after kicking.)
- The reason why you're dizzy is...
-  Yes?
that people kick with...
all their strength. Then it's hard to turn.
A person's centre of balance is in their head.
Turn your head first after kicking.
If I lose balance after kicking hard...
(His shoe tore.)
- This is bad.
-  It tore?
My shoe tore.
(He feels embarrassed.)
- Director.
-  Sorry.
Your power was too overwhelming.
(She clasps her hands politely.)
Goodness.
(What will happen to me?)
(The director smiles brightly.)
- Kick here?
-  Yes.
- Here I go.
-  All right.
Take it slow.
That's it. Great, great.
Look at the opponent and shoot lasers at him.
Shoot lasers. That's it.
Laser. That's it.
- Maintain your balance.
-  All right.
Many female actors do this kick.
It's the best type of kick to show off flexibility.
That's it.
That was the best so far.
That was the best kick you've ever done.
Keep your eyes on your opponent.
That's it. Use your other leg.
(His compliments make her feel more confident.)
(Her knee kicks are praised as well.)
- One more time.
-  All right.
Go for it.
I can do whatever is asked of me.
(I can do whatever is asked of me.)
I enjoy boxing.
I think that helped a lot.
From time to time,
I worry about the difficult action sequences.
However, the director kept complimenting me.
It made me want to do better.
It made me passionate about the action scenes.
There are acrobatic scenes in the movie.
- Acrobatics?
-  Yes.
Many martial artists are unable to do acrobatics.
- We'll start with basic rolling.
-  All right.
If I do that,
- the scene will be big.
-  Right.
They can widen the shot.
After the basics,
- let's keep going if you can.
-  All right.
This is one of the most common moves.
It shows off a woman's figure.
It's an acrobatic move called an aerial cartwheel.
(He demonstrates the aerial cartwheel.)
Another common move is a back handspring.
(This time, it's a back handspring.)
This is the most difficult move.
- Take a look.
-  Be careful.
(After the back handsprings, a turn in mid-air)
Can you do it?
Do I have to?
Those moves are really difficult.
I think it'll be so scary.
- This one is also...
-  I can't even start.
We'll make sure that you're safe.
- Try it slowly.
-  I think it'll make me dizzy.
I will be very dizzy.
(She'll start out slowly with rolling on the mat.)
- How do I do it?
-  Sit down first.
- From sitting down like this?
-  Yes.
Hold your knees and get up. Yes, that's it!
(That's it!)
(That encouraged her to keep doing it.)
Stop. You can stop now.
Gosh, I'm so dizzy.
- You did so well.
-  Did I?
You did such a great job.
I'm dizzy.
Now, let's try rolling backwards.
- Rolling backwards?
-  Yes.
- Sit down here first.
-  Is that how I start?
Yes, you have to sit down first.
In 1, 2 and 3!
Push! That's it!
Where am I?
(The entire world is spinning.)
- Where am I right now?
-  You did well.
That's it! Yes.
Great. That was awesome.
When is this needed by the way?
Why would I need this for action scenes?
- This is necessary...
-  Will I ever use this?
for you to move on to the next step.
- We just practised rolling.
-  Yes.
Let's use acrobatic moves like that...
to try learning a few things you can use for action scenes.
- Sure.
-  All right.
(First, fight according to the choreography.)
(Second, use the rolling move.)
- Your back must touch the surface.
-  It's higher than I expected.
(Will she be able to do this, too?)
- Yes. That's it!
-  Roll on your back!
- Impressive.
-  That was awesome.
(They cheer her on.)
You can do this...
because you're not scared.
It's not something you can do when you're scared.
It's...
- seriously...
-  Did I do a good job?
- Yes.
-  I don't really know what happened.
You don't, right? But you did great.
- Let's try one more time.
-  Sure.
All right. Ready...
(She's so nimble.)
Perfect! That was perfect.
- Nicely done.
-  Gosh, it hurts.
You actually have to wear knee and elbow pads for this,
- but this is a demonstration, so...
-  By the way,
- if there's a villain here...
-  You must kick him.
Can't I just come around...
and kick him like this?
Do I really have to roll like this before kicking him?
(You have a point.)
Most practical people like me would...
- You're right.
-  go up to the villain...
and kick him like this.
There's a huge gap between movies and reality.
It's very different.
(Now, I can understand.)
After this, we'll create a scenario and connect the moves.
That's why you're learning these moves.
If you can do these moves... We call it "choreography".
You'll learn the choreography and use these moves in it.
- Let's give it a try.
-  Okay.
We'll try a simple choreography with two main moves.
(Action actors will demonstrate first.)
(Beat the first villain.)
(Then beat the second one.)
Then you roll.
Let's go.
(Chae A confronts two villains.)
Get ready...
and go!
(She's serious.)
(She quickly beats both villains...)
(and rolls...)
(to attack an innocent civilian as well.)
Great. That was really good.
- Aren't you over-complimenting me?
-  You're so fearless.
No, you're really good at this. You make me want to teach you more.
Let's learn one more move, then.
I was going to make you practise a lot before teaching you this,
- I see.
-  but you're learning so fast.
I think I'll be...
- good at everything.
-  All right.
- Then let's get ready to move on.
-  I feel so confident right now.
Please demonstrate the move using the neck.
Ready,
action.
(Fly like a bee...)
(and wrap your legs around your opponent's neck.)
- This one will be very difficult.
-  It is, indeed.
I'm not kidding. It's one of the most difficult moves.
If you can pull this off,
you won't need a stand-in for action scenes.
Let's give it a try. I'll strongly recommend you...
to all film directors if you can do this.
Let's try wrapping your leg around his neck first.
- Okay.
-  Just that part.
Get ready.
In 1, 2 and 3!
Great! That's it.
- Twist your legs.
-  Turn your body...
Yes. Wrap both legs around his neck to...
That's it! You're doing great. I think you'll be able to do it.
Don't you think so?
Let's try it. I'll help you like just now, so let's...
give it a try. Do it slowly.
Think of this as a real shoot. Get ready.
Be serious.
Ready,
action!
I'm going to kill you all.
(They're impressed.)
We're so impressed.
You seriously won't need a stand-in.
I really mean it. I'm not lying.
- I was going to use wires.
-  Are you okay?
Are you all right?
I'm serious. I really think you can do it.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- It was fun.
-  You did such a great job.
- Thank you.
-  I'm impressed.
You surprised me.
He said that I'd be able...
to shoot action scenes without the need for a stand-in.
Hearing that...
was such a proud moment.
I'm quite ambitious, so I want to do everything myself...
without a stand-in. He said that it's definitely possible,
so that alone made today a great day.
Soon Shim.
Did you have a good day?
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
(She says hi to Soon Shim first.)
Goodness, I'm so tired.
(Then she heads over to her couch right away.)
Do you know what I did today?
Today,
I learned...
amazing combat moves for action scenes.
You'd never imagine me doing those moves.
Come over here, Soon Shim.
(Let me practise a move, too.)
I'm exhausted. My body aches, too.
(Come at me!)
Shall I put on the pain relieving patch?
(She grabs a pain relieving patch.)
I found one.
How am I going to put this on?
Soon Shim, put this on my back.
How am I going to do this by myself?
What should I do?
(She gets up to find a solution.)
(She tries to use the mirror,)
(but her attempt fails.)
I should put it right here.
This is a great idea.
I came up with an ingenious idea.
This is why great things...
(This is why great things...)
often come from desperation.
(Desperation can be a good thing.)
It's right here.
I got it.
I did it.
(Did she succeed without Soon Shim's help?)
Gosh, how can I fix this?
Oh, right. I should...
(She came up with another idea.)
Goodness, I'm in pain.
Soon Shim, you startled me.
(You startled me.)
(She took out a back scratcher.)
That worked. I got it right on the spot.
(This is why people need tools.)
Putting on the patch exhausted me even more.
Soon Shim, it'd be amazing if you could do things like this for me.
Don't you think so?
(I need to lie down.)
Soon Shim.
I'm hungry because I exercised intensely today.
What shall I eat?
Shall I get fried chicken and beer...
just for today?
Just today.
All right, I won't.
Soybean broth...
How many calories does a bowl of kongguksu have?
Let's eat kongguksu.
(Let's eat kongguksu.)
Soon Shim.
Make me a bowl of kongguksu.
(Soon Shim, make me a bowl of kongguksu.)
I tend to be very strict when I have to get ready...
for film or drama shoots.
Once, I didn't eat anything...
for about 5 to 7 days... prior to a shoot.
I am very strict about what I eat and losing weight.
Let's make kongguksu now.
I need one block of tofu...
and a handful of almonds.
While grinding them together,
I'll take agar-agar out.
Agar-agar strips.
I heard this has zero calories.
(Rinse agar-agar strips.)
I'll leave the strips to drain.
This is ready.
(Sniffing)
It doesn't smell that delicious.
(Put blended tofu and agar-agar strips in a bowl.)
(Then add cucumber slices as garnish...)
(and sprinkle sesame seeds.)
(No dish is complete before you take a photo of it.)
It looks absolutely delicious.
(Agar-agar is great for those who are looking to lose weight.)
(Her low-calorie kongguksu looks nutty and tasty.)
(Slurping)
(She tastes the soup, too.)
(Is it delicious?)
It tastes very healthy.
I only had one bite so far, but I already want to stop eating it.
(I don't want to eat this.)
Shall I add just a little bit of this?
(Shall I sprinkle a bit of salt?)
(She's torn.)
No.
(She managed to resist the temptation.)
Those who like soybeans would love this dish.
It's great for those who like tofu.
(The problem is that I'm not one of them.)
I got a lot of compliments today,
so I feel super confident right now.
(She studies the action scenes in the middle of eating.)
I want to become a great action actor.
(I want to become a great action actor.)
Soon Shim, does this mean I'll become...
Angelina Jolie of Korea?
(She's embarrassed.)
Did I go too far?
If you had seen what I did today,
you would've peed your pants.
(You would've peed your pants.)
If you'd been there to see what I did...
I got so many compliments today.
I really want to learn more.
First,
I'll practise rolling, which I got complimented on.
I'll roll on this.
Here I go.
Move over, Soon Shim. You'll get hurt.
(We can see how passionate she is about acting.)
I've been cast for a film.
It's my first film in about a year,
so there are many things that I need to prepare.
I'll also have to pull many all-nighters for the shoots.
Hence, I think I'll need to take a short break...
from I Live Alone.
I've decided to focus on the film for a while.
Through I live Alone, many people became interested...
in my lifestyle, and I received so much support...
as well as love.
When you live alone,
opportunities to look back and reassess your life...
don't come by easily, and you rarely get to make such efforts.
This show, I Live Alone,
gave me an opportunity to do just that.
I'm also glad that many people empathised with me...
and loved me being on the show. I must say that I am...
very grateful to have been a part of the show.
I'll work harder as an actor...
to come back to show you the better, newer me.
(Her cheery vibe and charisma...)
(will make her shine on the silver screen.)
What do you think?
That was hard.
I'm exhausted.
(Happy farewell with the action actor, Chae A)
(At Kim Ban Jang's house on an exciting day)
Make sure to include that and the tree in the frame.
(His front yard is filled with filming equipment.)
(There are so many people, too.)
Yes. Bring it down from there.
(Where is Kim Ban Jang, though?)
(We love you so)
I have to wear something that goes with the song.
(He puts it on the floor.)
(He lays them out on the floor to decide what to wear today.)
We're shooting a music video today,
and we decided to do it at my place.
I moved here about six years ago,
and I've never had so many people over at once like this.
I was thinking that it may look like a refugee camp.
It was very hectic.
(The current temperature is 36C.)
(There is no air conditioning at his house.)
It's so hot, isn't it?
Yes.
(The body heat from all the people makes it feel hotter.)
(I should turn on the fan.)
I don't even have an air conditioner.
I hope this cools you guys down.
I brought it from Hyun Moo's place yesterday.
You must need the fan, no?
I'll give it to you if you need a fan.
- Seriously?
-  Yes.
Thank you.
(All right.)
(He's grabbing a few other things.)
My place is very hot, isn't it? Do any of you need towels?
- Yes, thank you.
-  I'd love one.
Sure.
- Thank you.
-  Well...
- I'd like one, too.
-  Here you go.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
- Can I get one, too?
-  Of course.
- A little bit more.
-  You guys are working so hard.
Thank you.
Ban Jang, we need you in the frame.
(The shoot begins.)
We're ready now.
All right. Let's go.
Okay. Everyone, get ready.
Let's roll.
- Yes.
-  Action!
(That startled Ban Jang.)
(He starts singing.)
(He misses the first beat...)
(and sings lethargically.)
(His face looks tense, too.)
(It looks like today will be a long day.)
Cut!
- We'll take a short break.
-  Cut.
You look too tense right now.
- Please relax.
-  Relax and do whatever you want.
- Okay.
-  Good.
Everyone, let's go again. Get ready.
(Second attempt at the solo scene)
Action!
(Go away.)
(I need to relax.)
(Forcing himself to relax makes him more nervous.)
Stop!
- You look very awkward right now.
-  I see.
- You still seem tense.
-  Do I?
- Okay.
-  Your facial expressions...
are making you look very lethargic.
- Let's give it another try.
-  Sure.
All right.
(Grooving)
(That's pretty good.)
(His facial exercises seem to have worked.)
(He uses his hat to add a witty twist to the end of the scene.)
(He's finally feeling relaxed.)
Cut! Okay!
- That was good.
-  Yes.
(After the morning portion of the shoot)
(He rummages through something.)
They have to eat something.
Goodness, I ran out of rice.
I'm in trouble.
(I'm in trouble.)
(Running)
(Rushing)
(He's running at full speed, carrying his pot as a baton.)
(He arrives at a restaurant nearby.)
Hello, Sir.
I have guests over now and realised that I've run out of rice.
- I came to get some rice.
-  All right.
- I'll pay you back.
-  Shall I put it in this?
Yes, please. It's my pressure rice cooker.
(It's freshly cooked warm rice.)
I really appreciate it.
Yes.
- Thank you so much for this.
-  No problem.
Thank you again!
(Ban Jang's life is the epitome of slow life,)
(but he's running.)
(I must return before this rice gets cold.)
(He runs as fast as he can to feed his special guest.)
(Is the guest already here?)
(Who's the person that turned Ban Jang into Usain Bolt?)
Hello.
Hey, where were you?
I ran out of rice,
so I went over to a restaurant nearby to get rice.
What kind of dishes did you get?
I didn't buy anything. I made them all myself.
- You made them?
-  Of course. Why would I buy them?
I wouldn't have suggested eating at your place if that was the case.
I watch I Live Alone occasionally.
One day, I was watching it...
and was like, "My gosh. He's so quirky."
He lives with the nature,
accepting it as part of him.
As you can see, you fully enjoys his life.
I thought, "I want to work on a summer song with him."
That's how it began.
I asked around to get his phone number and reached out to him.
That's how we started working together. And oddly enough,
things just happened.
Everything has been going very swimmingly.
So you made all these dishes.
Of course.
If you eat it like this, it's very delicious.
I brought pickled laver...
as well as pickled chives.
- I will...
-  Let's eat.
go to my garden and pick some vegetables.
- What kind of vegetables?
-  I grow leafy greens.
- I'll be right back.
-  Okay.
I didn't look after it for a few days,
and it looks like the rain made the weeds grow so much.
What should I do?
I can't tell what's edible and what's not.
(I'm hungry.)
(What's taking him so long?)
Thanks for growing so well.
This spot doesn't even get much sunlight.
All right.
(This should be enough, right?)
- Did you wash them?
-  I should go do that now.
- Go rinse them.
-  Okay.
I'll be back shortly.
Cats hang out here, too. You have to wash them.
(Did you call me?)
(It's for the legendary diva.)
(I must make sure that they're perfectly washed.)
I told him to make sure they're clean, and he's taking 600 years.
(He's meticulously washing them one by one.)
(They're so clean now.)
Hurry up!
Come on!
- You washed them for 600 years.
-  Sorry.
I see lettuce and perilla leaves.
Is it a bowl for mixing them?
(He brought a handful of leafy greens.)
Let's put them in here like this.
- Oh, my. It looks amazing.
-  Let's eat.
- Thank you for bringing the dishes.
-  It looks delicious.
It's seasoned summer vegetables.
- How is it?
-  It's perfect for summer.
(He eats a whole pickled chilli pepper.)
It's spicy!
It's so delicious.
The chilli pepper is spicy.
It's an extremely spicy one.
(He seems to be enjoying it...)
(but quickly becomes silent.)
(There's a fire in my mouth!)
Isn't it very spicy?
I only eat a tiny bit of it at a time.
I eat 2mm of it for each bite.
(I won't forget this taste for 600 years.)
Try wrapping it in the vegetables.
It's so delicious.
(The wrap will put out the fire.)
- I've already...
-  Wait! Hold on.
Gochujang must be eaten...
with dried yellow croaker.
- Is it yellow croaker?
-  Yes. I tore it into strips.
Oh, my.
(Devouring)
(It's a combination of perilla leaves and dried yellow croaker.)
This tastes divine.
Does it?
It makes me feel alive.
- Does it enliven you?
-  Yes.
So do you never cook at home these days?
I don't have time to look at home at all.
I thought you'd at least make rice.
I feel bad that you didn't even have time to make rice.
I'm not sure if being super busy when you're young is a good thing.
I got surgery for cancer at the age of 30...
and was told I only had 3 months left to live.
Back in those days, I couldn't...
really work on a full stomach.
- Why not?
-  I felt that singing...
on an empty stomach would help me focus on the song better.
But after going through that at the age of 30,
I make sure to eat no matter what.
I never miss a mealtime.
- We work to live, you know?
-  Yes, that's right.
I started cooking for myself with that mindset...
when I was 30 years old.
(Hee Eun brought dishes she made to feed Ban Jang.)
- Feel free to eat more.
-  Okay.
- I want to...
-  Do you want to mix them with rice?
- I'll do it.
-  Okay.
(He gets up.)
Add a bit more rice. I'll eat some, too.
Gosh, bibimbap in a bowl like this is definitely a summer delicacy.
Let's mix everything now!
Here we go.
(The dish is ready.)
(Their mouths get filled...)
(with a perfect combination of flavours.)
The cicadas' cry is making me feel as though we're at a valley.
We're at a valley now.
Your place is right by a valley.
Bibimbap doesn't taste as good when you eat it alone.
It's tastes better when you share it with someone.
- It's like music.
-  That's right.
Everyone enjoyed working with you so much.
- Your members said that?
-  Yes.
Everyone says that I'm scary. Weren't they scared of me?
Why are people scared of you?
I don't know. Everyone thinks I'm scary.
- I'm not scared of you.
-  I know.
- I feel comfortable around you.
-  That's good.
For some reason, I feel like...
- I can call you in emergencies.
-  I'm your emergency contact.
You're like my mother.
You don't have to eat it all if you're full.
It's delicious.
(After the delicious lunch)
I should leave these with you.
- Really? You're giving them to me?
-  Yes, of course.
- Thank you so much.
-  You're welcome.
I made them for you anyway.
(I'll savour them.)
What's that beep?
- It's from my refrigerator.
-  Your refrigerator?
Is it because the door was kept open for too long?
It has artificial intelligence.
Oh, I see.
I'll return the containers to you later.
Sure, that's fine.
That should hold you up for a while.
- Just make rice.
-  Okay.
The problem with this house is the fact...
- that weeds grow so well here.
-  Yes.
I think it makes the house look a bit dark.
All sorts of weeds are growing freely.
- The trees should be pruned, too.
-  Yes.
- It'd be hard to cut the trees.
-  Yes. That will be hard.
You need to trim their branches little by little.
The bathroom is what concerns me the most.
- My bathroom?
-  You said it gets very cold.
A clean kitchen and bathroom are all you need.
- I can use it just fine.
-  It just gets cold in winter.
The only problem is that I don't have hot water.
Can you install a small furnace for hot water?
- I'm going to buy a water heater.
-  Water heater?
That's a good idea.
He has such a pure soul.
He's old enough to be my son,
but his soul is so pure that it makes me think...
he could be my grandson.
(He could be my grandson.)
He seems very naive,
but he's been figuring his life out on his own for a long time.
He's very independent and doesn't get swayed easily.
He knows exactly what he wants to do.
(They get a break before resuming the shoot.)
(He pours water.)
(He fills up the pot with water.)
(Will this enough?)
(They're making instant coffee.)
- Pour it here.
-  Okay.
- Isn't it hot? Be careful.
-  Yes. I'll do it.
Good. That should be fine.
- After that...
-  All right.
- I'll put all of these in, then.
-  Sure, go ahead.
Pour it
Add cold water if anyone says it's too strong.
(He's being very careful with them.)
It's so cold.
Be careful, Ban Jang.
Have some coffee, everyone.
It's not icy cold, but...
(Coffee is here.)
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
(He serves coffee to every single crew member.)
Have some coffee.
- Thank you.
-  No problem. I hope you enjoy it.
My place is very hot, and everyone was working so hard.
Seeing them sweat so much made me feel apologetic.
Hee Eun made coffee.
I boiled water and served the coffee.
It was such a hot day, so I'm not sure how helpful it was.
However, serving the coffee and watermelon to the crew members...
helped me feel better. I was happy to see the crew enjoying them.
- It looks airy and breezy.
-  I know, right?
(Goodness)
The mosquitos are acting up again.
Can someone pass me some tissue?
- Hey.
-  I got a bite, and it's bleeding.
I don't know what bit me.
(Hee Eun got a mosquito bite on her foot.)
(Let me see.)
(Ban Jang picks a leaf from a plant.)
Take this and...
- Does it help?
-  Yes.
- It repels mosquitos.
-  Really?
Mosquitos are funny because they don't bite me that much but...
- Do they mainly bite your guests?
-  Yes. They do.
That's enough.
- There are many mosquitos here.
-  Yes. There are so many mosquitos.
Let's go. Get ready.
- We're rolling.
-  Action!
(Hee Eun and Ban Jang start dancing together.)
- He's doing the dance again.
-  Hee Eun, you look so cute.
Backward and forward.
(But for some reason, it looks like folk dance.)
Cut! Stop.
- What's the problem?
-  Don't do the dance, please.
What is she referring to, exactly?
- It's when I go like this.
-  What?
- It's how old ladies dance.
-  I see, the grandmother dance.
(It's the second attempt at the dance scene.)
(Ban Jang starts moving his feet up and down in a strange way.)
(Hee Eun does it, too.)
No. Please stop.
It's looking like folk dance again.
Really? Okay. No folk dance.
That traditional beat sort of works for reggae music,
- so it comes out naturally.
-  You already tried it, though.
- Right.
-  All right, let's go.
- We're rolling.
-  Action!
(He moves his feet differently this time.)
(Their cute dance no longer looks like folk dance.)
I feel like we've become friends...
through working on the song together.
She's a legendary musician who has so much more experience than me.
So at first, I was very worried about how I should approach her.
But she's very open-minded,
so befriending her was easier than getting to know younger musicians.
We've gotten close through working on the song together.
I feel so comfortable around her and I had a lot of fun working with her.
(He got to spend the day with people...)
(he likes to sing and dance with.)
This breeze feels so nice.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
(Sharing the fun moments made Ban Jang's day even better.)
I don't know what to eat. There's nothing to eat in my refrigerator.
Shall I learn cooking?
We'll do it together, but please watch carefully first.
(He discovers his hidden talent.)
(She glances.)
- You're doing great.
-  Am I?
Yes. You seem to have a talent for this.
(Hyun Moo moves into his new house.)
(The excitement doesn't last long.)
(There's so much work to do.)
(When will I tidy up everything?)
(It's never-ending.)
I can't decide.
(The Two Men's Laborious Day)